- Where's Mon? - She's at home..
-摩妮卡呢？ -她在家…
putting up decorations for Rachel's birthday party tonight.
幫瑞秋今晚的生日派對做佈置
- You're not helping? - I tried..
-你不用幫忙嗎？ -我有試過…
but apparently singing "I Will Survive" in a helium voice, not helping.
但是很明顯地，用假音唱 「我會活下去」並沒有幫助
- Hey, guys. - Hey.
-嘿，你們好 -嘿
Don't say that loud. Gunther's gonna want to hug me.
別說那麼大聲，阿甘會過來抱我的
Good news, everyone. We finally found a nanny.
好消息，我們終於找到保姆了
- This is Molly. Molly, Chandler, Joey. - Hi.
-這位是莫莉，莫莉，錢德，喬伊 -嗨
Somebody's getting a little fussy.
有人有點不高興喔
You're damn right I am. I've been waiting for a cookie for seven minutes.
你說的沒錯，我就是不高興 我已經等餅乾等了七分鐘了
Okay. You know what, I'm just gonna take her outside.
好了，我想我帶她出去好了
- No, you stay. I'll do it. - Okay. Thank you.
-不，你留下來，我去 -好的，謝謝
- Nice to meet you guys. - Yeah, you too.
-很高興認識你們 -是啊，我們也是
- Wow, Molly's just great. - Yeah.
-哇，莫莉真的很不錯 -是啊
Yes, bravo on the hot nanny.
是啊，真棒，請了個辣保姆
- What? You really think she's hot? - Are you kidding?
-什麼？你真的覺得她很辣嗎？ -你看不出來嗎？
If I wasn't married, she'd be rejecting me right now.
如果我未婚，她現在就在拒絕我了
Joey?
喬伊？
How do you think she's doing?
覺得她的姿勢怎樣？
Am I the only one that doesn't think she's hot? Ross?
我是唯一不覺得她辣的嗎？羅斯？
- I mean, she's not unattractive, but.. - Right.
-我覺得她不算是沒有魅力，但是… -沒錯
but hot?
但是算辣嗎？
Thank you.
謝謝你
Now that Rachel's gone?
瑞秋走了，說吧？
So hot, I cried myself to sleep last night.
她真辣，我昨晚是哭著入睡的
The One With Phoebe's Rats
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Hey, Mike, what's the capital of Peru?
嘿，麥克，秘魯的首都是哪呢？
- Lima. - No.
-利馬 -不是
It starts with a V and ends with an X.
是V開頭X結尾的字
And hopefully with a T-O in the middle.
然後最好中間有T跟O
You know, come to think of it, the capital of Peru is "Vtox."
我仔細想想之後，我想秘魯的首都 應該叫做「VTOX」
- Oh, God! - What?
-喔，天啊！ -怎麼了？
Okay. I don't want to freak you out or anything..
好了，我不想要嚇壞你
but I just saw a rat in your cupboard.
但是我剛在櫃子裡看到一隻老鼠
Oh, yeah. No, that's Bob.
喔，是喔，那是霸柏
Well, he's your pet rat?
是你的寵物鼠嗎？
Well, not so much a pet as, you know, an occasional visitor..
不太算是，只是偶爾會來拜訪
who I put food out for. Kind of like Santa.
我有時候會餵他 有點像聖誕老公公
Except Santa doesn't poop on the plate of cookies.
除了聖誕老公公 不會在餅乾盤裡便便以外
You can't keep a rat in your apartment. They're unsanitary.
你不能在公寓裡養老鼠 那很不衛生的
I mean, they transmit leptospirosis and hantavirus.
我是說，他們可能會 傳染細螺旋體病或是漢他病毒
- What are those? - I don't know..
-那是什麼？ -我不知道
but they don't sound like spa treatments.
但是聽起來可不像是水療吧
- You have to get rid of it. - Okay, fine.
-你必須要處理掉他 -好啦
If it means that much to you, I'll get rid of Bob.
如果你這麼在乎，我會處理掉霸柏的
Thank you.
謝謝你
It's so weird you think he's so gross, yet you're willing to eat his crackers.
真奇怪，你覺得他很噁心 卻又在吃他的餅乾
- Hello. - Hello.
-哈囉 -哈囉
Gavin, I just want to say thank you again..
蓋文，我想再次跟你道謝
for watching Emma yesterday during the presentation.
謝謝昨天幫我照顧艾□
I really owe you an apology.
我真的需要跟你道歉
- For what? - When we first met, you know..
-道什麼歉？ -當我們第一次見面時，你知道的…
I thought you were pompous and arrogant and obnoxious.
我以為你是自負、高傲又討人厭的人
Is this your first apology?
這是你的第一個對不起嗎？
No, I just mean, you know, first impressions don't mean anything.
不，我是說第一印象 通常不是很重要的
And I think you're a really good guy. And I'm sorry that I misjudged you.
而我認為你是個好男人 很抱歉我錯看了你
- Morning. - Hello.
-早安 -哈囉
But you know what? Hey, new day, new leaf.
但是你知道嗎？ 新的一天，新的開始
I am just really, really happy..
我只是真的很高興…
I'm sorry. Obviously, Heather's ass has something more important to say..
我很抱歉，很明顯地，海瑟的屁股 有更重要的事要對你說
so I'll just wait till it's finished.
我先讓它說完好了
- What? - I was giving you an apology..
-什麼？ -我正在跟你道歉…
and you were totally checking her out.
而你一直在打量她
I wasn't. I'm in fashion. I was looking at her skirt.
我沒有，我是在時裝業工作 我只是在看她的裙子
Or was it pants? I didn't really see what happened below the ass area.
還是褲子呢？我並沒有看清楚 屁股以下的部位
Wow, you are really.. You're really a creep.
哇，你真的是… 你真是小人
What do you care if I was looking at her?
就算我是在看她，你又在乎什麼呢？
Are you jealous?
你是在忌妒嗎？
Oh, yeah. I'm jealous.
喔，是啊，我好忌妒
"Oh, Gavin. Please, please look at my ass."
「喔，蓋文，拜託請看看我的屁股」
Stop looking at my ass!
不要看我的屁股！
I mean, I just think you are totally inappropriate. Okay?
我只是認為這樣的行為是不妥的
This is a work environment. She's your subordinate.
這是工作場所，她是你下屬
But it was okay when you slept with your old assistant, Tag?
但是你跟你前助理泰格上床 卻是可以的？
That is totally different for two reasons.
那是不一樣的事，因為兩個原因
One: I didn't know that you knew that.
一：我不知道你知道這件事
And two: I wasn't some creep staring at his ass.
二：我不是盯著他屁股看的小人
We had a.. We had a deep, meaningful relationship.
我們有很深入、有意義的交往
What was Tag's last name?
泰格姓什麼？
It was..
姓…
Oh, my God.
喔，我的天
He didn't.. He didn't.. He didn't have a last name.
他沒有…他沒有… 他沒有姓
It was just Tag, you know, like Cher or..
只是叫泰格而已，你知道的 就像雪兒或是…
you know, Moses.
摩西一樣
But it was a deep, meaningful relationship.
但是那是很深入、有意義的交往
You know what? My first impression of you was absolutely right.
你知道嗎？我對你的第一印象 完全正確
You are arrogant. You are pompous. Morgan! Morgan!
你很高傲，你很自負 摩根！摩根！
- Tag's last name was Morgan! - It was Jones.
-泰格姓摩根！ -是瓊斯
What are you, his boyfriend?
你是誰啊？他男朋友嗎？
（中央咖啡廳）
- Man, I wish I had a nanny like you. - You mean when you were a baby?
-天啊，我希望我有個像你一樣的保姆 -你是說在你小時候嗎？
Sure.
當然
Would you stop staring at her?
你可不可以別再盯著她看？
I wasn't staring.
我沒有盯著
I was leering.
我是斜眼瞄著
What's the big deal with her?
她有什麼了不起的呢？
Maybe she's attractive in an obvious kind of way.
或許她有很搶眼的魅力
Yeah, obvious beauty's the worst.
是啊，很搶眼的魅力最糟糕了
You know, when it's right there in your face.
你知道的，當它就顯現在你面前時
Me, I like to have to work to find someone attractive.
我比較喜歡漸漸去發掘一個人的魅力
Makes me feel like I earned it.
讓我感覺像是我辛苦得來的
Looks like Joey's doing all right with her.
看起來喬伊好像跟她處的不錯
Yeah. Hey, that was nice of you guys to back off..
嘿，你們兩個這次願意退讓出…
and let Joey get the girl for once.
讓喬伊去泡她，真是好心
- I'm gonna take her to the apartment. - Okay. I'll be home right after work.
-我要帶她回去了 -好的，我下班之後就回去
- Okay. - Okay, bye, Emma.
-好的 -好的，艾□再見
I love you.
我愛你
- Bye. - Bye.
-再見 -再見
They've elected me to talk to you about the baby talk.
他們推派我來跟你說 你模仿嬰兒說話的事
It's not so good.
大家不是很喜歡
I think it's sweet.
我覺得挺可愛的
Bye, Emma!
再見，艾□
Hey, listen, Joey. About Molly, I would really prefer if you didn't go after her.
嘿，喬伊，關於莫莉 我希望你不要去動她
- Why not? - It took months to find a good nanny.
-為什麼不行？ -因為我們花了好幾個月才找到好保姆
And I wouldn't want anything to, you know, drive her away.
而我不希望有任何事情讓她離開
So you think I'm just gonna sleep with her..
所以你認為我只會跟她上床
and never call her again, and things are gonna get uncomfortable?
之後就不再打電話給她 讓一切都變得很尷尬嗎？
Yeah, that sounds about right.
是啊，聽起來好像也對
Come on, there are plenty of other women out there.
別這樣，外面到處都是女人
Just forget about her, okay? She's off-limits.
忘了她好嗎？她不是你可以要的
Oh, man! What'd you have to go and say that for?
天啊！你為什麼要這樣說呢？
Now that you told me I can't have her, makes me want her even more!
你這樣說之後，我就更想要她了
- What are you, a child? - Yes!
-你還是小孩啊？ -是的！
It's true. He's like a little boy, like Ben.
沒錯，他就跟小孩一樣，像班
Just think of him as a really, really, really horny Ben.
想像他就是很色、很色、很色的班
No!
不對！
Look, Joey, come on now. For me, please.
聽著，喬伊，別這樣，為了我，拜託
Just try to focus your sexual energy on someone else.
把你的性能量轉移到別人身上
Fine.
好啦
Take me home.
帶我回家吧
Do you want a piece of this?
你想被書K嗎？
- Hey, Mikey. - Hey, Phoebe.
-嘿，麥克 -嘿，菲比
- What are you doing? - Setting rattraps.
-你在做什麼呢？ -放捕鼠器
- To kill Bob? - No. No, to test his neck strength.
-要殺霸柏嗎？ -不是，只是測試一下他脖子有多硬
No, I don't want to kill him. I thought we were gonna capture him..
不，我不想殺死他 我以為我們要活抓他
and, you know, set him free in the countryside..
然後到鄉下把他放生
where he could meet a friendly possum..
讓他可以認識友善的大老鼠
and a wisecracking owl.
還有愛說笑的貓頭鷹
- Okay, okay. I'll throw away the traps. - All right, I'll find Bob. I'll get him.
-好了，我把捕鼠器丟掉 -好，我會找到霸柏，我會抓到他的
Bob? Bob?
霸柏？霸柏？
Robert?
羅伯特？
Wait, I think I hear him.
等等，我聽到他的聲音了
Oh, my God! Bob had babies! Bob's a mom!
天啊！霸柏生小孩了！ 霸柏當媽媽了！
We'll have to think of a new name.
我們得替她改名字了
I don't know, I kind of like "Bob" for a girl.
我不知道，我喜歡「霸柏」當女生名字
No, no. I mean, I'm not sure that we..
不不，我是說我不確定我們…
Oh, my God. We killed Bob?
天啊，我們殺了霸柏嗎？
Well, maybe it wasn't Bob. Maybe it was a mouse.
或許不是霸柏，或許只是隻老鼠
Susie?
蘇西？
That's it?
就這樣？
It's over?
結束了嗎？
Who shot J.R.?
誰殺了小傑？
I have got to get a job.
我得要找份工作了
What's up?
怎麼了？
Seriously, dude. Three years ago.
真的，老兄，三年了
Listen, can you do me a favor? I'm gonna be out today.
聽著，你可以幫我一個忙嗎？ 我今天要出去
Can you keep an eye on Joey..
你可以幫我看著喬伊
make sure nothing happens between him and Molly?
確保他跟莫莉之間不會出事嗎？
- You don't trust him? - Well, no.
-你不相信他嗎？ -嗯，不相信
Some woman who sounded a lot like Joey called earlier..
昨晚有個聽起來 很像喬伊的女人打電話來
and asked for her daughter, the "hot nanny."
要找她那個叫做「辣保姆」的女兒
Is this your long-term plan, for me to run interference?
你打算讓我長期干預他們嗎？
Because I could get a job any day now.
我可能隨時都會找到工作的
You do appear right on the cusp of something.
你在職場上可真是炙手可熱
Look, come on, man. I'm sure he'll lose interest in a week or two..
聽著，拜託 我確定他一兩星期就會沒興趣了
but for now, could you please just do this for me?
但是現在，你可以幫我這個忙嗎？
Fine, but don't blame me if it doesn't work.
好啦，但是如果失敗可別怪我喔
Because you know once Joey sets his mind on something..
因為你也瞭解，喬伊一旦下定決心
more often than not, he's going to have sex with it.
無論如何，他都會把她搞上手的
Well, I mean, we've gotta do something. Okay?
那我們得要做點什麼，不是嗎？
Nannies like her don't grow on trees.
像她那樣的保姆是不會 憑空出現在樹上的
- Picturing that tree? - I am, yes.
-在想像那棵樹嗎？ -是的，沒錯
Where you going, Joe?
你要去哪？喬伊
For a walk.
去散步
You mind if I join you?
我也去好嗎？
Actually, I'd rather be alone. You know, I really need to organize my thoughts.
事實上，我想要一個人去 我真的需要理清一些想法
Your thoughts?
一些想法？
Plural?
複數的？
All right, fine. I only have one thought.
好啦，我只有一個想法
It's about the hot nanny! I gotta see her!
就是關於那個辣保姆！我必須見到她！
- I'm afraid I can't let you do that, Joe. - Now you're saying I can't see her?
-恐怕我不能讓你去，喬伊 -你是說我不能見她？
You're killing me! She's forbidden fruit! It's like, like..
你是在害死我！她是禁果！這就像…
like she's the princess and I'm the stable boy.
她是公主而我是馬童
Look, I know. She's the most beautiful woman in the world.
聽著，我知道她是世上最漂亮的女人
I can hear you.
我聽見了
Could you set my pillow and blanket on the couch for me, please?
你可以幫我把枕頭跟毛毯 鋪到沙發上嗎？
Why are you doing this, huh?
為什麼你要這樣？
Did Ross tell you not to let me go over there?
是不是羅斯要你別讓我過去的呢？
Yes, as a matter of fact, he did. So I can't let you go.
沒錯，事實上就是 所以我不能讓你過去
Interesting. Now there are obstacles.
有趣，現在出現阻礙了
Hot nanny and me against the world!
辣保姆跟我一起抵抗全世界！
This is the stuff great novels are made of.
這就像偉大的愛情小說
- Great novels? - Fine. Mediocre porn.
-偉大的愛情小說？ -好啦，二流的情色書刊
- Gavin Mitchell's office. - Rachel Greene's office.
-蓋文米丘辦公室 -瑞秋葛林辦公室
Give me that phone.
電話給我
Hello, this is Rachel Greene. How can I help you?
哈囉，我是瑞秋葛林 可以為您效勞嗎？
Okay then. I'll pass you back to your son.
好的，我會把電話傳給你兒子
Hey, Mom. No, that's just my secretary.
媽，不是，她只是我的秘書
Excuse me, Gavin. I have a question I need to ask you.
對不起，蓋文 我有個問題必須要問你
Mom, I'll call you later. Yeah.
媽，我再回電給你，是的
- Yes? - If you like looking at butts so much..
-怎樣？ -如果你那麼喜歡看屁股…
why don't you just go look in a mirror?
你何不自己去照鏡子呢？
Thank God you finally said that.
感謝上帝，你終於說了
I saw you make a note on your pad three hours ago.
三個小時前我就看到 你寫在筆記本上了
- Man, I really bug you. Don't I? - Oh, no. Please..
-天啊，我真的惹你厭，是不是？ -喔，不，拜託…
I don't care about you enough to bug me.
我根本不在乎你，更別提討厭你
In fact, from now on, I'm going to take the high road..
事實上，從現在開始 我會表現的很有格調
and I'm going to be very, very nice to you, you mama's boy..
而且我會對你非常好 媽媽的乖寶寶…
starting right now.
從現在開始
- Hey, Rach. - Hi.
-嘿，瑞秋 -嗨
- Ready for your birthday lunch? - I am.
-準備好要吃生日午餐了嗎？ -好了
But first, Monica, I would like to introduce you..
但是首先，摩妮卡 我想要介紹你認識…
to my very talented colleague and more importantly..
我非常能幹的同事，而且更重要的是…
my wonderful friend, Gavin Mitchell.
我的好朋友，蓋文米丘
- Pleased to meet you. - Pleased to meet you.
-幸會 -幸會
Are you coming to Rachel's party?
你會來參加瑞秋的派對嗎？
Oh, no, no, no, no. Gavin can't. He already has plans..
喔，不不不不，蓋文沒有辦法 他已經有計劃了
most likely with his mother.
應該是要去看他媽媽
I don't mind. I'll cancel them. I would never miss my secretary's birthday.
我不介意，我可以取消 我不想錯過我秘書的生日
Why did you invite him? I can't stand that guy!
為什麼你要邀請他？ 我無法忍受那個男的！
- You were being so nice to him. - I was faking it.
-你看起來跟他很好啊 -我是裝出來的
Can't you tell when I'm being fake?
你難道看不出來我是裝的嗎？
Hey, Mr. Phillips. Nice suit.
嘿，菲利浦先生，很好看的西裝
Right there. That was so fake!
抓到了，真是好假！
Hey, Chandler, which do you like better..
嘿，錢德，你比較喜歡…
the tuna tartare or the mushroom empanadas?
鮪魚派還是烤蘑菇餃？
- The pile of raw fish, or the tacos? - Oh, the tacos. Definitely, the tacos.
-一堆生魚還是墨西哥手卷？ -喔，手卷，當然是手卷
I still can't believe you invited Gavin.
我真不敢相信，你邀請了蓋文
He is just the last person I want to see.
他是我最不想見到的人
You're welcome for the party. I'm glad you're having a good time.
安排派對的事，不用跟我客氣 我很高興你喜歡
I hope he doesn't show up. Of course he won't, the guy hates me.
我希望他不要出現 他當然不會，他討厭我
- Does he? - What?
-是嗎？ -什麼？
Maybe he keeps bothering you so much because he likes you.
或許他一直惹你生氣 是因為喜歡你
It's like in first grade when Skippy Lange would push me..
就像在小學一年級的時候 史基藍吉會推我…
because he secretly had a crush on me.
其實是因為他在暗戀我
Monica, you think Skippy liked you?
摩妮卡，你以為史基喜歡你嗎？
Honey, all those boys had a bet to see if he could knock you over.
親愛的，所有的男生都在打賭 看他是不是有辦法撂倒你
- She's out. I'm gonna take her home. - Okay. Thank you.
-她睡了，我帶她回去 -好的，謝謝
Bye, sweetheart.
再見，甜心
Do you see what all the guys see in her?
你有在她身上看到 那些男人看到的東西嗎？
Wouldn't kick her out of bed.
不會想要踢她下床的
No more vodka for me.
我不可以再喝伏特加了
Hey, Rach. So can I sing "Happy Birthday" to you now?
嘿，瑞秋，現在可以 唱生日快樂歌了嗎？
- Yeah, sure. - All right.
-當然可以 -好的
See you later.
待會見
Hey, Rach. Somebody got you shoes.
瑞秋，有人送你鞋子
Give me!
給我看！
- Wow. Wow. Oh, my God! - Careful! Careful!
-哇哇，我的天啊！ -小心！小心！
These are my rat babies!
這些是我的老鼠寶寶！
Yeah. We have rat babies now.
是啊，我們現在有老鼠寶寶了
You brought rats to my birthday party?
你帶老鼠來參加我的生日派對？
So this is what a stroke feels like.
我感覺像是中風一樣
Well, I had to bring them. We killed their mother.
我必須要帶著他們 我們殺了他們的媽
They're our responsibility now.
他們現在是我們的責任了
You know, they require constant care. You should know that, you're a mother.
你知道的，他們需要一直被照顧 你應該知道的，你自己也是母親
Are you comparing my daughter to a rat?
你把我女兒跟一隻老鼠做比較？
No. Seven rats.
不，是七隻
We should take them home. We need to feed them.
我們應該帶他們回家了 他們需要吃東西了
You're gonna leave my party to take care of a box of rats?
你因為要照顧這盒老鼠 而離開我的派對？
Well, I'm sorry, Rachel, but I'm not like you. Okay?
嗯，我很抱歉，瑞秋 但是我不像你，好嗎？
Not everyone can afford help.
不是每個人都請得起幫手的
Hey, where the hell are Joey and Molly?
嘿，喬伊跟莫莉去哪了？
I asked you to watch them.
我要你看住他們的
I'm sorry. I got a little preoccupied.
我很抱歉，我有點分心了
Look, we have to stop them before something happens.
聽著，我們要在發生事情前阻止他們
Right behind you, big guy.
我會跟隨你的，大哥
So you see, Molly, what people don't understand..
所以你瞧，莫莉 人們不瞭解…
is that acting is a discipline. It takes a lot of hard work.
演戲是一種紀律，是很辛苦的工作
- So where'd you study? - I didn't go to college.
-所以你是在哪裡學的？ -我沒有上大學
- No, where'd you study acting? - Molly, people don't study acting.
-那，是從哪裡學會演戲的呢？ -莫莉，演戲不是學來的
Molly, do you mind giving us just a minute?
莫莉，可以讓我們談幾分鐘嗎？
- Sure. I'll go check on Emma. - Thanks.
-當然，我去看艾□ -謝謝
Will the stable boy never get the princess?
馬童就不能得到公主嗎？
What do you think you were gonna do, have sex with her here on my couch?
你以為你是在做什麼？ 在我家沙發上跟她作愛？
No. The leather sticks to my ass.
不，沙發皮會黏住我的屁股
This isn't fair. What makes you think I'm gonna sleep with her..
這實在不公平，你憑什麼認為 我會跟她上床…
and then blow her off, huh?
然後就拋棄她呢？
Can't you guys open your minds to the possibility that I actually like her..
你們難道不能敞開心胸接受 或許我是真的喜歡她…
and might want something real?
而且要的是真感情？
Look, the truth is, I haven't felt this way about anyone since Rachel.
聽著，事情是，自從瑞秋之後 我就沒有對任何人有過這種感覺了
Okay? I didn't think I could ever love again.
好嗎？我以為我不能再愛人了
- Come on! - Joe!
-少來了！ -喬伊！
Hi. Is Molly here?
嗨，莫莉在嗎？
Yeah, yeah. Come on in. Molly?
在，請進，莫莉？
- Hey. Guys, this is Tabitha. - Hey.
-嘿，各位，這位是塔比莎 -嘿
- I'll see you tomorrow. - Okay.
-明天見 -好的
Well, Joey, I guess we have no problem.
嗯，喬伊，我猜我們沒事了
It's like my favorite fairy tale come true.
這就像是美夢成真
The princess, the stable boy and the lesbian.
公主、馬童跟女同性戀
Okay. Okay, you start preparing the formula..
好了，你先泡牛奶
and I'll start changing the box.
我去換盒子
And then we gotta put them straight to bed.
然後就送他們上床睡覺
When did we become one of those couples..
為什麼要讓我們的愛情生活…
whose lives revolve around their rats?
環繞著老鼠呢？
Well, you know what? They're our responsibility now.
你知道嗎？他們現在是我們的責任了
Okay, fine. These rats are our responsibility.
好的，這些老鼠是我們的責任
What happens when they mate and there are hundreds?
要是他們交配後 變成上百隻呢？
Mate? They're all brothers and sisters.
交配？他們是兄弟姐妹耶
Yeah, not such a problem with rats.
是啊，但是對老鼠可不是問題
No, they're more of a "love the one you're with" kind of animal.
他們是「愛上誰就上誰」的那種
No. Really?
才不，真的嗎？
Oh, my.. Get off your sister!
喔…不要搞你姐姐啦！
Oh, my God. What are we gonna do?
我的天，我們該怎麼辦呢？
The.. We have seven rats.
我們有七隻老鼠
So, what if each of them has seven rats..
如果七隻老鼠的每一隻…
and then each of those has seven rats? That's like..
都再生七隻，那就是…
That's math I can't even do!
我不會算數學！
What are we gonna do?
我們該怎麼辦呢？
Well, I know this is gonna sound crazy..
嗯，我知道這聽起來很瘋狂…
but we could not let the box of rats ruin our lives.
但我們可以不讓這盒老鼠 毀了我們的生活
Yeah, okay. I guess you're right.
是啊，好吧，我想你說的對
All right, so we should just give them away.
好了，我們必須要送走他們
But to nice families with children and reduced-fat Wheat Thins.
但要送給有小孩 還有低脂餅乾的好人家
Those were Bob's favorites.
那些是霸柏最喜歡的
It's gonna be okay.
會沒事的
- You must think I'm crazy. - No, I think you're sweet.
-你一定認為我瘋了 -不，我覺得你很善良
Good. This is just so hard. It's hard for me to let them go.
這真是很難，好難割捨
I guess it just brings back memories, you know..
我猜這讓我聯想起很多往事
from when I gave birth to my brother's triplets and I had to give them up.
就像我懷了我弟的三胞胎 最後還是必須送回給他們養
I haven't told you about that yet, have I?
我沒有告訴過你那件事嗎？
Thanks for the party, honey. Should I help you clean up?
謝謝你幫我辦派對，親愛的 我應該幫你打掃嗎？
No way. You had your party. Now I have mine.
不要，你的派對結束了 現在換我的
- Is everything all right? - I just get bummed..
-一切還好吧 -我只是有點累
when my birthday's over.
生日結束了
Well, at least you have one thing to be happy about.
至少有一件事值得你高興
That jerk, Gavin, from your office didn't show up.
你辦公室那個渾蛋蓋文沒有來
Yeah, I hate him.
是啊，他好討厭哦
We weren't talking about you. We were..
我們不是在說你，我們…
No. No way to recover. No. Okay.
好吧，來不及轉了，算了
- Fun party. - Well, it was.
-一定很好玩 -嗯，是的
And you would have seen it if you didn't show up at..
你本來會看到的，如果你出現在…
9:30?! God! This party was lame.
九點半？天啊！這派對糟透了
Again, you're welcome!
再一次，不用客氣！
- Look, I'll just give you this and go. - You bought me a present. Why?
-聽著，我只是要給你這個就走人 -你買禮物給我，為什麼？
Let me explain how birthday parties usually work. There are presents..
讓我解釋一下生日派對 是怎樣的情況，通常有禮物…
and a cake, perhaps a fourth or fifth person.
有蛋糕，或許還有第四個或第五個人
Okay, I..
好的，我…
I got you the present to make up for being such a jerk to you.
我送禮物給你 彌補一下我對你的惡劣
Well, okay. Well, that's very nice. And you wrote a card.
嗯，好的，真好，而且你還寫了卡片
- "From Gavin." - I really mean it.
-「蓋文贈」 -肺腑之言
It's beautiful.
很美耶
If you don't mind..? Let me.
如果你不介意… 讓我來
Well, what do you know, it fits.
誰知道呢，非常合適
See, Gavin. You're capable of being a nice guy.
瞧，蓋文，你是可以當個好男人的
Why do you give me such a hard time?
為什麼你要刁難我呢？
I'm not sure.
我不知道
Well, Monica seems to think it's because you have feelings for me.
摩妮卡好像認為 是因為你對我有感覺
I do have feelings for you.
我是對你有感覺
- You do? - Yes. I feel that you're a little annoying.
-真的嗎？ -是的，我覺得你很煩人
See, why? Gavin, why?
為什麼？蓋文，為什麼？
Right when I'm about to change my opinion of you, you go and you..
就在我要對你改觀的時候，你就…
And you do that.
你就這樣做了
Hey. Listen, I think I left something here.
嘿，聽著，我有東西忘了帶走
Well, somebody left this. Is this yours?
是有人忘了這個，是你的嗎？
No, but I like it.
不是，但是我蠻喜歡的
No, I think I left one of my rat babies.
有一隻老鼠寶寶我忘了帶走
Well, no. I haven't seen it, but if I do, I'll let you know.
沒，我沒有看到 但是如果有，我會讓你知道
Rat baby! Rat baby! Rat baby! Rat baby!
老鼠寶寶！老鼠寶寶！老鼠寶寶！
Maybe that's him.
或許就是他